Before I go have my night cheese and go to bed, I just wanted to shout y'all out because I said the same thing about billionaires on Threads that I said here.
And once again, Threads proves itself to be a low vibrational nail salon because the responses are so startlingly different.
The vibration and the intellectual level, the comprehension, the critical thinking here in my Instagram is so compared.
And not only are they ill-equipped, they are loud and ignorant and even mean about it.
So kudos to y'all IG.
I never thought I'd see the day, but we did it.
We did it.
I'm definitely deactivating my Threads because there's a bunch of idiots over there.
In my support of Palestine, in my just being a decent human, I lost a lot.
I lost a lot of money.
I lost agents.
I lost the publicist.
I lost opportunities.
And I have to say it was all worth it.
Don't clap for me because that's what I'm supposed to do.
Thank you.
We are stardust floating up.